A Guide to the National Committee on United States-China Relations records, RG 1, Accession 1 FA772
Rockefeller Archive Center
- Exchanges - General, 2
  - Ms. ZHU Qing (Beijing Foreign Affairs Vocational Senior High School), 2000-2001; FA772:157; Still image (Box 149, Folder 2093)
    1 snapshot of Zhu with Zhou Xinwen.
  - Mr. ZHU Ruzhong (Yangzhou Middle School), 2000-2001 (Box 140, Folder 2094)
  - Mr. ZHU Ruzhong (Yangzhou Middle School), 2000-2001; FA772:158; Still image (Box 149, Folder 2094)
    6 images of Zhu sightseeing and with Guo Yi and class.
  - Ms. ZHU Shanping (Nanjing Foreign Language School), 2000-2001 (Box 140, Folder 2095)
  - Ms. ZHU Shanping (Nanjing Foreign Language School), 2000-2001; FA772:159; Still image (Box 149, Folder 2095)
    16 snapshots of Zhu and classroom.
  - Mr. ZHU Wanli (Shijiazhuang No. 42 Middle School), 2007-2008 (Box 140, Folder 2096)
  - Ms. ZHU Yan (Suzhou No. 6 Middle School), 2003-2004 (Box 140, Folder 2097)
  - Mr. ZHU Yu (Suzhou Middle School), 1997-1998 (Box 140, Folder 2098)
    Science Skills Center High School, Brooklyn, NY. File includes one snapshot of his classroom (retained in file).
  - Mr. ZHU Zhenyang (Suzhou Middle School), 2010-2011 (Box 140, Folder 2099)
  - Mr. ZHU Zhenyang (Suzhou Middle School), 2010-2011 (Box 140A, Folder 2099A)
  - Ms. ZHUANG Xiaoyan (Suzhou Middle School), 1999-2000 (Box 140, Folder 2100)
    John Browne High School, Flushing, NY.
  - Ms. ZHUANG Xiaoyan (Suzhou Middle School), 1999-2000; FA772:160; Still image (Box 149, Folder 2100)
    2 snapshots (learning to drive, with Margot Landman.
  - Mr. ZOU Lingyun (Chongqing No. 8 Middle School), 2006-2007 (Box 140, Folder 2101)
    Assignment not known.
  - Ms. ZOU Meili (Dalian Computer Vocational Middle School), 2003-2004 (Box 140, Folder 2102)
  - Ms. ZOU Renli (Xinghai School, Suzhou Industrial Park), 2008-2009 (Box 140, Folder 2103)
  - Mr. ZOU Zhongmin (Hefei No. 10 Middle School), 2010-2011 (Box 140, Folder 2104)
  - Mr. ZOU Zhongmin (Hefei No. 10 Middle School), 2010-2011 (Box 140A, Folder 2104A)
  - Teachers Exchange Program - Guidelines for American Host Schools and Families, 1997, undated (Box 140, Folder 2105)
  - Teachers Exchange Program - Information for Chinese Teachers, 1990s-2000s (Box 140, Folder 2106)
    Information on applying for social security numbers, library cards, and New York driver's license.
  - Teachers Exchange Program - Chinese Exchange Teachers, 1996-1997, 1997-1998 (Box 140, Folder 2107)
    List of teachers and American school assignments.
  - Unlabeled VHS Tape, Slip case numbered 16829, Undated; FA772:166; AV - VHS Tape
    Slip case numbered "16829."
  - Cherry Creek Schools, "A Year in Suzhou - China Teacher Exchange", Undated; FA772:167; AV - VHS Tape
    Produced (?) by Cherry Creek Schools, Denver, CO.
  - Nova (PBS), "Rainbow Bridge," Town of Jinze (Shanghai, PRC), 2000; FA772:168; AV - VHS Tape
    VHS tape and box also labeled "Eric Zinn, ACLS, 2000."
  - A Glimpse of China - Newton, MA - Beijing Jingshan Educational Exchange, Undated; FA772:169; AV - VHS Tape
    Copyright Phil Henderson.
  - To Taste a Hundred Herbs, Undated; FA772:170; AV - VHS Tape
    No information on contents or date.
  - KidsFirst, North Woods China Segment, 2003 March; FA772:171; AV - VHS Tape
    North Woods International School, La Crosse, WI. Five minutes.
  - Performance, Product and Beyond - Arts Education in the School District of La Crosse, Undated; FA772:172; AV - VHS Tape
  - La Crosse, Wisconsin, Schools, 1996 October; FA772:173; AV - VHS Tape
    19:00 minutes.
  - Karen Levin, Experience China, 1997 November; FA772:174; AV - VHS Tape
    Two programs: Teaching and Learning (13 minutes), Sights and Sounds (20 minutes). Karen Levin, a West Middle School teacher in the Cherry Creek School District shares her teacher exchange experience in China.
  - The China Symposium, 2004 December 4; FA772:175; AV - VHS Tape
    Identification taken from label on slip case. No further information available.
  - Title in Chinese characters, Undated; FA772:176; AV - VHS Tape
    Title appears to describe two sections.
  - Title in Chinese characters, 1998; FA772:177; AV - VHS Tape
  - Bangor, ME, Program on Gao Chengchun and Wang Xiuzhen, 2002-2003; FA772:178; AV - VHS Tape
    Gao and Wang were exchange teachers in the Bangor Public Schools during the 2002-2003 school year.
  - Jackson Middle School, Portland, OR, and Milton Public Schools, Milton, MA, Undated; FA772:179; AV - VHS Tape
- Exchanges to China, 3
  - Historic Preservation Study Team - Briefing and Debriefing, 1982 May 14-June 2 (Box 29, Folder 571)
  - Historic Preservation Study Team - Brochure, 1982 May 14-June 2 (Box 29, Folder 572)
  - Historic Preservation Study Team - Correspondence (Pre-Trip), 1982 May 14-June 2 (Box 29, Folder 573)
  - Historic Preservation Study Team - Follow Up, 1982 May 14-June 2 (Box 29, Folder 574)
  - Historic Preservation Study Team - Itinerary, 1982 May 14-June 2 (Box 29, Folder 575)
  - Historic Preservation Study Team - Nominations, 1982 May 14-June 2 (Box 29, Folder 576)
  - Historic Preservation Study Team - Report, 1982 May 14-June 2 (Box 29, Folder 577)
    File includes a printed report on the trip.
  - Think Tanks - Background, Planning, and Invitations, 1983 May 9-24 (Box 29, Folder 578)
    The NCUSCR sent a delegation of U. S. Foreign Affairs experts to China, May 9-24, 1983.
  - Think Tanks - Bios and Namelist, 1983 May 9-24 (Box 29, Folder 579)
    Includes small headshot portrait photos.
  - Think Tanks - Report and Follow-Up, 1983 May 9-24 (Box 30, Folder 580)
  - Think Tanks - Report and Follow-Up, 1983 May 9-24; FA772:024; Still Image (Box 146, Folder 580)
    2 polaroid prints of unidentified Chinese and American participants.
  - Reading Study Team - Background and Planning, 1984 May 10-31 (Box 30, Folder 581)
    Study Group on Reading Skills Acquisition. The tour received funding from the Office of Educational Research and Improvement, at the U. S. Department of Education. The project anticipated a reciprocal visit of Chinese educational experts to the United States.
  - Reading Study Team - Briefing and Debriefing, 1984 May 10-31 (Box 30, Folder 582)
  - Reading Study Team - Brochure and Namelist, 1984 May 10-31 (Box 30, Folder 583)
  - Reading Study Team - Itinerary and Follow-Up, 1984 May 10-31 (Box 30, Folder 584)
  - Reading Study Team - Report, 1984 May 10-31 (Box 30, Folder 585)
  - Black University Presidents - General, 1984 August 27-September 9 (Box 30, Folder 586)
    Delegation of Presidents of Historically Black Colleges. File includes Namelists, Bios, and Brochure. The file includes a descriptive itinerary / report on the trip.
  - Black University Presidents - Briefing, 1984 August 27-September 9 (Box 30, Folder 587)
    The file also includes a report on the trip by Cheryl Brown.
  - Black University Presidents - Reports and Follow Up, 1984 August 27-September 9 (Box 30, Folder 588)
    The file contains a cover page, but no final report.
  - Economic Think Tank - Background and Planning, 1984 November 27-December 16 (Box 30, Folder 589)
    American Economists Study Team.
  - Economic Think Tank - Debriefings, 1984 November 27-December 16 (Box 30, Folder 590)
  - Economic Think Tank - Papers, 1984 November 27-December 16 (Box 30, Folder 591)
    Includes notes on meetings.
  - Economic Think Tank - Report and Itinerary, 1984 November 27-December 16 (Box 30, Folder 592)
  - Economic Think Tank - Thank You and Follow-Up, 1984 November 27-December 16 (Box 30, Folder 593)
  - South Asia Specialists - Background and Planning, 1986 January 5-24 (Box 31, Folder 594)
    South Asian Studies Delegation
  - South Asia Specialists - Briefing, 1986 January 5-24 (Box 31, Folder 595)
  - South Asia Specialists - Brochures and Bios, 1986 January 5-24 (Box 31, Folder 596)
  - South Asia Specialists - Trip Report, 1986 January 5-24 (Box 31, Folder 597)
  - American Corporate Economists - Background and Planning, 1986 May 23-June 1 (Box 31, Folder 598)
  - American Corporate Economists - Brochure and Namelist, 1986 May 23-June 1 (Box 31, Folder 599)
  - American Corporate Economists - Itineraries, Follow-Up, and Report, 1986 May 23-June 1 (Box 31, Folder 600)
  - American Corporate Economists - Supplementary Material ("Joint Venture Agreements in the PRC"), 1986 May 23-June 1 (Box 31, Folder 601)
    File title supplied in processing. File contains manuscript on Joint Venture Agreements, 1985, plus reports of the American Economists' Study Team, November 29-December 15, 1984.
  - Education Administrators Delegation, 1986 June 16-July 7 (Box 31, Folder 602)
    Study tour to China, June 16 - July 7, 1986.
  - Technology Transfer Study Team - Background and Planning, 1987 July 26-August 9 (Box 31, Folder 603)
    Includes namelist and brochure.
  - Technology Transfer Study Team - Follow-Up, 1987 July 26-August 9 (Box 31, Folder 604)
  - Aspen Institute - National Committee Tour - General, 1987 October 21-November 11 (Box 31, Folder 605)
    Material from folder labeled "Correspondence with Chinese" added to file.
  - Aspen Institute - National Committee Tour - Lampton and Berris Trip, 1987 October 29-November 6 (Box 31, Folder 606)
    Original folder labeled "Correspondence with Participants." File contains itinerary for David M. Lampton and Jan Berris trip to Beijing concerning NCUSCR program directions. Material may be misfiled in this series; not really an exchange program.
  - Congressional Workshop Delegation - Background and Planning, 1988 April 12-23 (Box 31, Folder 607)
    Workshop program on the Role of Congress in U.S. Foreign Policy.
  - Congressional Workshop Delegation - Book, 1988 April 12-23 (Box 31, Folder 608)
    File includes The Role of the U.S. Congress in the American Foreign Policy Process, ed. Wang Xi., plus a study on the Sino-American textile trade. Both published by Fudan University Press.
  - Congressional Workshop Delegation - Briefing Material, 1988 April 12-23 (Box 31, Folder 609)
  - Congressional Workshop Delegation - Itinerary, Reports, and Follow-Up, 1988 April 12-23 (Box 31, Folder 610)
  - Congressional Workshop Delegation - Namelists, Bios, and Brochure, 1988 April 12-23 (Box 32, Folder 611)
  - Congressional Workshop Delegation - Notes on Selection of Participants, 1988 April 12-23 (Box 32, Folder 612)
  - Congressional Workshop Delegation - Original Papers, 1988 April 12-23 (Box 32, Folder 613)
  - Congressional Workshop Delegation - Papers, Introduction, and Questions in Chinese, 1988 April 12-23 (Box 32, Folder 614)
  - Sovietologists Study Group - Background and Planning, 1988 June 16-July 1 (Box 32, Folder 615)
    Sino-Soviet-American Relations Study Group to the PRC and the Soviet Union. File includes Briefing Agenda.
  - Sovietologists Study Group - Brochure, Namelist, and Itinerary, 1988 June 16-July 1 (Box 32, Folder 616)
  - Sovietologists Study Group - Follow-Up and Reports, 1988 June 16-July 1 (Box 32, Folder 617)
  - Sovietologists Study Group - Meeting Notes, 1988 June 16-July 1 (Box 32, Folder 618)
  - National Council on Measurement in Education Tour (Cancelled), 1988 September 13- October 4 (Box 32, Folder 619)
  - Productivity Workshop - Background and Planning, 1988 November 6-19 (Box 32, Folder 620)
    Multicity workshop program on "Enhancing Productivity and Competitiveness." Cosponsored by the China Enterprise Management Association. File includes materials from 1987-1988.
  - Productivity Workshop - Background and Planning, 1988 November 6-19 (Box 32, Folder 621)
  - Productivity Workshop - Correspondence, 1988 November 6-19 (Box 32, Folder 622)
  - Productivity Workshop - Papers, 1988 November 6-19 (Box 32, Folder 623)
    File contains participants' papers and Chinese translations. Also includes some bios.
  - Productivity Workshop - Report and Itinerary, 1988 November 6-19 (Box 33, Folder 624)
  - Youth Leaders Delegation - General, 1989 April 4-18 (Box 33, Folder 625)
    U.S. - China Emerging Leaders Program (American Center for International Leadership). This visit reciprocated the visit to the U.S. of the All-China Youth Federation in November 1988.
  - Youth Leaders Delegation - Bios, 1989 April 4-18 (Box 33, Folder 626)
  - Youth Leaders Delegation - Follow Up, 1989 April 4-18 (Box 33, Folder 627)
  - National Committee on American Foreign Policy Member Trip (Cancelled), 1989 April 30-May 20 (Box 33, Folder 628)
    An earlier trip, planned for May 1988, was similarly postponed. Materials pertaining to this have been added to this file.
  - Lampton and Barnett Trip - General, 1989 September 10-23 (Box 33, Folder 629)
    Trip by Davd M. Lampton and Doak Barnett for discussions with the Chinese People's Institute of Foreign Affairs and others on U.S. - China relations with the state of U.S. - China realtions.
  - Lampton and Barnett Trip - Report, 1989 September 10-23 (Box 33, Folder 630)
  - Coastal Development Study Group - Background and Planning, 1989-1990 (Box 33, Folder 631)
    The Study Group on Coast Economies and Development in China trip, originally planned for June 10-28, 1989, was cancelled in the wake of the Tiananmen Square uprising on June 4, 1989. A successor Study Group on Coastal Economic Development Strategy traveled to China on January 2-21, 1990.
  - Coastal Development Study Group - Correspondence (Outgoing), 1989 (Box 33, Folder 632)
  - Coastal Development Study Group - Correspondence (Incoming), 1989 (Box 33, Folder 633)
  - Coastal Development Study Group - Namelist, Program, Itineraries, and Reports, 1989-1990 (Box 33, Folder 634)
  - Coastal Development Study Group - Participants (Correspondence and Bios), 1989 (Box 33, Folder 635)
  - Coastal Development Study Group - Pre-Departure Briefing, 1989 (Box 33, Folder 636)
  - Coastal Development Study Group - State Planning Commission Correspondence, 1989 (Box 33, Folder 637)
  - Coastal Development Study Group - Final Report, 1990 (Box 33, Folder 638)
  - Coastal Development Study Group - Follow-Up Correspondence, 1990 (Box 34, Folder 639)
  - Coastal Development Study Group - Paper, 1990 (Box 34, Folder 640)
    Paper on "China's Coastal Development Strategy and Pacific Rim Free Trade Block," by Gang Zou and Jun Ma, July 1989.
  - Lampton and Berris Trip to Hong Kong, 1990 March 5-8 (Box 34, Folder 641)
    David M. Lampton and Jan Berris, breakfast and luncheon meetings.
  - The United States and the Future of Hong Kong Conference - Background Material for Participants, 1990 March 26-31 (Box 34, Folder 642)
  - The United States and the Future of Hong Kong Conference - June Y. Mei, 1990 March 26-31 (Box 34, Folder 643)
  - The United States and the Future of Hong Kong Conference - Namelists, Itineraries, Speeches, 1990 March 26-31 (Box 34, Folder 644)
  - The United States and the Future of Hong Kong Conference - Participants, Bios, 1990 March 26-31 (Box 34, Folder 645)
  - The United States and the Future of Hong Kong Conference - Planning and Background, 1990 March 26-31 (Box 34, Folder 646)
    "The United States and the Future of Hong Kong: Promoting Growth and Stability," March 29-30, 1990. Dinner and reception hosted on March 28 by the NCUSCR and the American Chamber of Commerce.
  - The United States and the Future of Hong Kong Conference - Report, 1990 March 26-31 (Box 34, Folder 647)
  - Interior Economics and Development Study Group - Background Readings, 1990 October 12-November 1 (Box 34, Folder 648)
    Study group on Interior Economics and Development in China.
  - Interior Economics and Development Study Group - Correspondence with State Planning Commission and China, 1990 October 12-November 1 (Box 34, Folder 649)
    Study group on Interior Economics and Development in China. Correspondence with State Planning Commission and other Chinese officials. Mainly follow-up correspondence.
  - Interior Economics and Development Study Group - Itinerary, 1990 October 12-November 1 (Box 34, Folder 650)
  - Interior Economics and Development Study Group - Participants, 1990 October 12-November 1 (Box 34, Folder 651)
  - Interior Economics and Development Study Group - Participants (Development), 1990 October 12-November 1 (Box 35, Folder 652)
    File concerns efforts to identify select candidates for participation in the study group.
  - Interior Economics and Development Study Group - Final Report, 1990 October 12-November 1 (Box 35, Folder 653)
  - Middle East Study Group - Jan Berris Working File, 1991 January 2-16 (Box 35, Folder 654)
    Delegation of American Middle East specialists. Area Studies exchanges cosponsored by the Ford Foundation. The trip was originally planned for 1989, but was put on hold following the Tiananmen Square uprising. File includes diary pages.
  - Middle East Study Group - Hong Kong and Taiwan Visit, 1991 January 17-19 (Box 35, Folder 655)
  - Middle East Study Group - Itinerary and Follow-Up, 1991 January 2-16 (Box 35, Folder 656)
  - Middle East Study Group - Participants, 1991 January 2-16 (Box 35, Folder 657)
    Biographical material for Robert and Sharon Freedman, Farhad Kazemi, John and Judith Kolars, Ira Lapides and Brenda Webster, and Ann Lesch.
  - Middle East Study Group - Predeparture Briefing, 1989 June 2, 1991 (Box 35, Folder 658)
  - Middle East Study Group - Trip Notes, 1991 January 2-16 (Box 35, Folder 659)
  - Urban Management Workshop - Background and Planning, 1991 January 28 -February 10 (Box 35, Folder 660)
  - Urban Management Workshop - Follow-Up and Thank-Yous, 1991 January 28 -February 10 (Box 35, Folder 661)
  - Urban Management Workshop - Namelist, Final Itinerary, and Report, 1991 January 28 -February 10 (Box 36, Folder 662)
  - Urban Management Workshop - Papers, 1991 January 28 -February 10 (Box 36, Folder 663)
  - Urban Management Workshop - Papers (in English and Chinese), 1991 January 28 -February 10 (Box 36, Folder 664)
    File includes papers presented by Chinese participants (in English) and Chinese translations of papers by U.S. participants.
  - David Gergen Trip - Background and Planning, 1991 April 11-19 (Box 36, Folder 665)
    Luce Scholar David Gergen lectured in China and Hong Kong on "The New World Order."
  - David Gergen Trip - China, 1991 April 11-19 (Box 36, Folder 666)
  - David Gergen Trip - Itinerary and Follow Up, 1991 April 11-24 (Box 36, Folder 667)
  - David Gergen Trip - Hong Kong, 1991 April 22-24 (Box 36, Folder 668)
  - David Gergen - Publication of New World Order (Box 36, Folder 669)
  - Japan Study Group - Communications with Chinese People's Institute of Foreign Affairs, 1991 May 12-24 (Box 36, Folder 670)
    Workshop on Changing Relations among the Powers in Northeast Asia.
  - Japan Study Group - Namelist, Itinerary, and Final Report, 1991 May 12-24 (Box 36, Folder 671)
  - Japan Study Group - Papers, 1991 May 12-24 (Box 36, Folder 672)
    Original papers and Chinese translations.
  - Japan Study Group - Participants, 1991 May 12-24 (Box 36, Folder 673)
  - Maritime Law Consulting Group, 1991 June (Box 36, Folder 674)
  - Environmental Conference - General (Namelist, Background and Plannning), 1991 June 28-July 14 (Box 37, Folder 675)
    "Local Economy and Global Ecology" multicity workshop.
  - Environmental Conference - Background Papers and Report, 1991 June 28-July 14 (Box 37, Folder 676)
  - Tibet Study Group - General, 1991 July-August (Box 37, Folder 677)
  - Tibet Study Group - Follow-Up and Report, 1991 July 28-August 7; 1999 (Box 37, Folder 678)
  - Tibet Study Group - Ford Foundation Proposal, 1988 (Box 37, Folder 679)
    Proposal to the Ford Foundation for a Binational Working/Study Group on Tibet, October 10, 1988. The proposal was also submitted to the United Board for Christian Higher Education in Asia.
  - Tibet Study Group - Funding, 1988-1991 (Box 37, Folder 680)
  - Former Soviet Union Workshop - Planning, 1992 February 17-March 1 (Box 37, Folder 681)
  - Former Soviet Union Workshop - Background Materials, 1992 February 17-March 1 (Box 37, Folder 682)
  - Former Soviet Union Workshop - Follow-Up, 1992 February 17-March 1 (Box 37, Folder 683)
  - Former Soviet Union Workshop - Namelists, Itinerary, Notes and Report, 1992 February 17-March 1 (Box 37, Folder 684)
  - Former Soviet Union Workshop - Namelists, Itinerary, Notes and Report, 1992 February 17-March 1; FA772:025; Still Image (Box 146, Folder 684)
    Two 7x10 color photos of delegation members, including Gail Lapidus, Marshall Shulman, Abe Becker [sic], and others.
  - Former Soviet Union Workshop - Participants, 1992 February 17-March 1 (Box 37, Folder 685)
  - Former Soviet Union Workshop - Hong Kong and Taiwan, 1992 February 25-27, February 27-March 1 (Box 37, Folder 686)
  - Greater China - Background and Planning, 1992 March 15-29 (Box 37, Folder 687)
    Study Team on Economic and Social Change in East Asia. Traveled to China, Hong Kong, and Taiwan.
  - Greater China - Delegation Members, 1992 March 15-29 (Box 38, Folder 688)
  - Greater China - Namelist, Itineraries, and Report, 1992 March 15-29 (Box 38, Folder 689)
  - Greater China - Hong Kong and Taiwan, 1992 March 24-29 (Box 38, Folder 690)
  - Daniel Boorstin Visit - General, 1992 March 30-April 17 (Box 38, Folder 691)
    Visit to China, March 30 - April 15, and to Hong Kong, April 25-27.
  - Daniel Boorstin Visit - General, 1992 March 30-April 17; FA772:164; Audiovisual - Two cassette tapes, numbered 1 and 2. (Box FA772:164, Folder 691)
    Daniel Boorstin talk, China and Beijing, March-April 1992.
  - Daniel Boorstin Visit - Itineraries and Brochure, 1992 March 30-April 17 (Box 38, Folder 692)
  - Board Trip - General, 1992 April 29-May 10 (Box 38, Folder 693)
    NCUSCR Board Delegation, led by chair Raymond Shafer and chair elect Barber Conable Jr.
  - Board Trip - Hong Kong, 1992 April 29-May 10 (Box 38, Folder 694)
    Includes various contact and name lists.
  - Board Trip - Planning and Arrangements, 1992 April 29-May 10 (Box 38, Folder 695)
    Includes a few thank-yous.
  - Board Trip - Planning and Arrangements, 1992 April 29-May 10; FA772:026; Still Image (Box 146, Folder 695)
    Group photo, Meeting at Zhongnanhai with Jiang Zemin.
  - Board Trip - Beijing Reception, 1992 May 8 (Box 38, Folder 696)
    Great Wall Sheraton Hotel.
  - Board Trip - Beijing Reception, 1992 May 8 (Box 38, Folder 697)
  - Board Trip - Beijing Reception, 1992 May 8 (Box 38, Folder 698)
  - Trade Policy Workshop - Articles, 1992 May 21-June 3 (Box 39, Folder 699)
    Multi-city Workshop on U. S. Trade Policy. Articles and clippings for briefing and background.
  - Trade Policy Workshop - AT, 1992 May 21-June 3 (Box 39, Folder 700)
    AT&T and the State Science and Technology Commission held an Intellectual Property Rights symposium in Beijing on May 19-22.
  - Trade Policy Workshop - Background and Planning, 1992 May 21-June 3 (Box 39, Folder 701)
    Multi-city Workshop on U. S. Trade Policy.
  - Trade Policy Workshop - Short Listed Candidates, 1992 May 21-June 3 (Box 39, Folder 702)
  - Trade Policy Workshop - China Council for the Promotion of International Trade (CCPIT), 1992 May 21-June 3 (Box 39, Folder 703)
  - Trade Policy Workshop - Delegation Members, 1992 May 21-June 3 (Box 39, Folder 704)
  - Trade Policy Workshop - Follow Up and Thank You, 1992 May 21-June 3 (Box 39, Folder 705)
  - Trade Policy Workshop - Papers (in English and Chinese), 1992 May 21-June 3 (Box 39, Folder 706)
  - Trade Policy Workshop - Report and Final Itinerary, 1992 May 21-June 3 (Box 39, Folder 707)
  - Trade Policy Workshop - William Zarit, 1992 May 21-June 3 (Box 39, Folder 708)
    Multi-city Workshop on U. S. Trade Policy. File includes edited copies of workshop papers.
  - Environmental Information Exchange Delegation, 1992 September 5-18 (Box 39, Folder 709)
  - Economic Development and Human Rights - General, 1992 November 27-December 10 (Box 39, Folder 710)